A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, South and Southeast Asia, Karachi and Islamabad, Pakistan, Field Office Files FA647
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, II
  - A Report of The Afghan Institute of Technology, Nov 1952; Photos (Box 19)
  - East Bengal Polytechnic Institute -- Dacca -- Report, Oct 1955 (Box 19)
  - Grant Projects -- Technical Education -- Oklahoma A&M Grant, Sep 1954-Dec 1955 (Box 19)